now I'm realizing I didn't know what
these are called mastermind for better
technical come up with a name later
change the title so I am joined today by
my brother Adriel and we are just we are
starting a mastermind type group a group
for goal-setting of technology projects
that have a higher purpose than just
being there for profit they're there to
serve humanity they're there to make the
world better more environmental whatever
the purpose is that's their first
priority and we each have a project that
falls under that category and we would
love other people to be able to join us
in the future who also want a space to
co-create crowd-source problems with
their project and just hold each other
accountable feels like it's a little bit
too too authoritarian but just be a
space to say yes this is what I
committed to it got done or it didn't
get done and here's why
and I could really use help with this
piece and helping each other create
projects that are here for purpose
instead of profit yes you just came in
okay being spoke okay cuz I'm on I'm on
life thank you
close my door okay hand it to me I'll
turn it on and so yeah you don't have my
fingerprint oh okay here you go that's
why that's why it's like okay I can use
a phone for what kay please go and close
my door okay close my door thank you
alright back to back to the purpose
instead of instead of parenting we're
sort each gonna take a turn to introduce
nurse this is how these meetings are
gonna go we're gonna take a turn to
introduce ourselves say what our project
is and this is the first week so next
the future weeks we'll be saying what we
had committed to and why it got done if
it got done and why did or why didn't
get done and then we will have a
discussion where people are able to
bring to the table
anything that they would like help
working on from each other or from the
crowd that are watching and then we will
at the end write down
and verbally say I will write it down so
I can remember what we're committed to
doing for the next week and anyone who
would like to join and has a project
that is for purpose and is a technology
project is invited to come and
participate if you think this would be a
positive space for you something that
you can gain gain insight and
accountability from so a trio would you
like me to go first and introduce my
project or would you like to go first
all right so I'm Jubilee this is my
youtube channel of crowd democracy I am
creating a technology cooperative that
we all own together that's operated with
transparency and democracy but that is
what I am doing with already two people
we're meeting on Fridays and doing that
at 11:00 a.m. Pacific Standard Time
working through the process of creating
our first project which actually is the
idea Cafe and that's the project I'm
focusing on in these Saturday mornings
which is a little confusing because I'm
focusing on creating the YouTube channel
idea cafe a space that is for
conversations that I want to participate
in and finding ways to work through
having people working through my
limitations figuring out why I can't
seem to get three people on camera and
while ago a few weeks without it and so
growing that YouTube channel I think has
a lot of potential both for the
cooperative and for me and that is what
I am what I'm here to do and also to
support my my brother who has an amazing
project and anyone else because I know
there are so many projects out there
right now and people who care about
creating a better world and I want to be
able to use whatever brain power I have
to help facilitate them and be present
for their projects in whatever format
they're currently and that is me and a
lot faster than five minutes all right
hi everyone my name is adria and the
project I am starting is called
a collection really short form it's a
project to fight its information
initially it will be focused on politics
and science two fairly disconnected
things but you might be able to see how
they overlap so on the politics side
I've been summarizing it as it's a bit
like IMDB for politics so the idea is
each politician each politician would
have their own page where it's just an
ongoing tally of things they've done
things they voted on things they haven't
voted on and then a summary of sort of
what that means about that person so
what sort of the values you can guess
they might have based on how they voted
and things they've done and that sort of
thing there's also sort of another piece
to that where it's helping to manage it
elections so as we get a bigger list of
all the politicians when people are
running in elections it gives an easier
way to compare all the options for
voters in the election then on the other
side of that there's the sort of there's
the science part where it's about I
guess did discussing in reviewing
different forms of content initially it
will be things like scientific studies
where the community would take it apart
and answer different questions about it
at things like was the experiment design
properly was a conducted properly who
paid for it that type of thing and then
the end goal of that is to have you know
a large library of scientific studies
reviewed by the community towards a
certain topic for example vaccines so
that we can start to answer common
questions you know with some actual
proof behind it that people can dive
deeper into if they feel the need
awesome Thanks we both did that in much
under five minutes we'll see if we later
on and we're also talking about our what
we committed to the previous week I'm
sure we will go longer the other things
we didn't discuss one of the reasons
this started was last Friday you and I
were having a conversation that lasted
for four hours and every time we have a
conversation we are creating technology
that isn't necessarily arts projects but
just like little oh yeah we could create
that and we
create that and so I wanted to also
showcase a bit of that one of the things
we didn't discuss is how long we want
the actual live portion of this to go
not four hours I'm I'm thinking we might
want to keep the live version today at a
half an hour and then in the future when
there's more of us up to an hour I would
I would say yeah I think that make sense
all right sounds good we are trying to
be Joe Rogan why not why not come on
five hours of let's just let's just hash
this out which is great we end up going
that that on Fridays we went over our
hour for sure
which is fine the time commitment to
create that sure so what are you you
don't have stuff to commit to anything
in the next week but what is something
that is like what's a barrier what's
something that is stopping you from
moving forward just deciding what's next
so of course as you know you know I had
not bad traction for a while I was
posting every I was listening to twice a
week on with the election sort of
discussing and showing people the the
prototypes that are available and then I
decided to move and that ended up taking
a ferret my time and all the things
involved in that and now that that's
done getting back into it before I
stopped I did sort of actually finish
out that part of it where I finished
that portion of discussing the
politician history prototype and so now
my thing is trying to figure out what
comes next I got a few different ideas
and it's just sort of figuring out where
the value is what actually seems like it
might produce something that sort of I
guess did the the the most useful and
then actually started to work on that
all right I don't know if I can help you
with that but sometimes just discussing
it and hearing right things right gives
you the okay here's the next the next
thing I don't even I know so I had idea
cafe I had everyone every week and then
I struggled with with getting people to
that same timeslot and so I switched the
format so that I was finding one person
picking a question finding a time and
then putting it out so that you
and that format worked except that I
stopped doing it like that I kind of cuz
like I had this vision other people
would be contact and be like I want to
discuss X and that didn't happen so I
have to keep reaching you know and I
have to just own that I have to be like
okay this needs to be a bit of a prior a
bit of a priority even though I have
this global tech thing that I'm trying
to create as well and that is what I've
been doing I've been having
conversations with B people and starting
the Friday morning conversation and so I
want to be able to focus on both of
those things and so having how do I get
people to the idea cafe how do I find
that one person co-create a question
pickup time that is easier for me
because I need things to be easy and I
have a few ideas of how like today I'm
gonna post on one of the parentid groups
that only allows you to post things
about projects and anything spammy on
Saturdays and so I want to focus on on
that I'm also a little bit all over the
place at the idea cafe which I don't
think is a bad thing because I'm all
over the place like I've had ones on
donor conception on mental health on
autism I would love to have one on brain
injury or brain tumors I want to have
hey Ernesto I want to be able to have so
finding like literally any topic there's
also other topics like one of my friends
is Kurdish right word and you know
they're going through a genocide right
now and I reached out to him and asked
like does he know anyone like I wouldn't
participate in the conversation but like
facilitating conversations between other
people that are powerful they don't have
anything to do with me how do how do we
talk about about things that are that
are happening right now and are huge and
how do we witness that and like I can
see how powerful it is to have a
platform for a conversation that's why
that's becoming our first project with
together tech that we're creating the
platform for idea cafe but for the
YouTube channel to get bigger and I
think there's a lot of potential in it
because when I was doing it for those
few weeks we grew from zero subscribers
to 30 subscribers which doesn't sound
big but this channel has been up for a
long
and it's taken me a long time to get a
sixty subscribers and when I post
something people watch like it'll have
about ten people watch it maybe that one
has thirty people watch it every time
and the way that it's formatted it's
just like you bring your influence
because you're coming off of whatever
that doesn't mean you need to bring
influence with you but you're bringing
it you're sharing it with everyone else
and so I was also reaching out to people
I enjoy watching on YouTube and people
who are more influencers to ask them to
come on idea cafe more in a video format
and more so other people could find me
but also possibly doing that more
finding people that are more middle line
influencers that aren't you know I mean
they don't have millions of subscribers
but have like ten tens of thousands of
subscribers and asking about you okay
it's more about the conversation and not
it's not trying to build an audience but
if that happens not to get mad about it
no and that's why is the audience seems
to be engaged because there's more views
than on these ones and so having that be
part of part of part of like how do I
get people there how do i how do I do it
with it like I said within my
limitations of needing it to be
stress-free and easy and finding the
next piece that gives me that that was
what happens when I changed the
iteration but then I was and I had three
that week and I was like okay maybe also
when I have three in a week almost
saving them to be posted till the next
week in the next week so that I always
have one week so that it's it's constant
there's also a piece like when I was
doing it live on at 11:00 a.m. on
Wednesdays it's nice to have people
watching and participating people more
likely to watch live but also some of
the conversations aren't is appropriate
for life and so having them without
people commenting and then posting it is
actually it's you know they're gonna be
posted it's not like at the end you got
to be like everyone else was
participating too you don't then get to
say it's not posted but it's different
than having people watch it lives it's a
different feeling so I need to pick I
need to pick which one which one it is
and I think not live and then posting
live makes no sense I think and also I
as your audience gets
it becomes more useful to do live
because if you want live because of that
conversation obviously you're going to
have more conversation if you go live
and a thousand people see see that your
live versus 30 yeah yeah I'm like a big
YouTube person I follow a you know a
fair number of channels on YouTube and
one person thinking of in particular
always post you know on a certain day
but then they go live on technically
it's a different channel theirs but they
go live randomly and everything done yet
so they have the option to do that ya
know and that's always that's part of
the struggle is getting any kind of
audience getting any kind ofor like you
are sharing influence and you are being
able to like I get that when people look
at idea cafe channel they're like why
would I come on it there's 30
subscribers and I'm like right but it's
brand new and it's about like having fun
what makes this enjoyable and they not
ironic but the amazing thing about it is
everyone who's been on it even people
who are like I was super nervous I
didn't I didn't think didn't know how
this was gonna go afterwards in the
conversation because we need to take
turns sharing for five minutes on the
question and then we have an open
discussion for the rest of the half an
hour and they've all basically said in
the conversation like this was fun like
this is I want to do this again and
that's a piece of it too is keeping the
same people like reaching out to the
same autistic people and then also
finding other people right like like
growing that conversation so that I
don't have to keep finding new people
but the audience will be will hopefully
bring in new people so if you're your
Google you're searching for autistic
contents and then you watch us you're
like I want to I want to participate
right I want to be able to have those
conversations
then contacting contact I think the
truth is besides putting my email in
there I don't really know how to do
contact on YouTube right like even like
in my description I can put the email
but I think people aren't as likely like
they just want to comment but that they
can't comment with their email so I
can't even reach out to them to be like
yeah come participate so part of its
those limitations yeah I'm not sure that
do that I mean like as
you said YouTube comments I've seen some
people try to reach out to channels fit
that way right yes you can you know you
post your Twitter and stuff like that
and people can slide in your DMS but
Matt that's true I have for everyone
that that I do but here's my and I do do
that but I also do that after the fact
and I think doing it for the life Oh
though if we're not going live it
doesn't matter and that's a part of not
going live to issues to being able to
put in our full description before it
goes I've liked before it goes public
from private and then and then doing it
that way makes make sense and so I'm
getting getting some ideas what to do
for this coming week all right how about
you what is your are you thinking of
next next steps like you said yeah sure
so the next steps that I have in mind
one is to start working on the the
election piece with the US election we
were to say coming up when it's like a
year away but I mean that takes more
than a year so starting to build out the
election summary I mean that's a
especially useful on the Democratic side
where there's still a bunch of
candidates even though a couple people
who have dropped out I think it still
might be 10 or more I'm starting to
build that out and starting to figure
out what common questions there are what
content is supporting it actually build
the prototype like it would be for that
and actually you know it could be useful
for some people but mostly it's just
approved the concept there is to work on
the prototype for the article review is
that sort of the postal the least far
along and one of the harder things to
explain but also means more people
involved because I'm not a scientist and
the end goal is to have a couple
scientists on board that can actually
you know figure out what would be
involved in reviewing what could you
actually pull out and figure out what
sections are what and what is this just
somebody
was used to working with data and not
you know science stuff that maybe I just
misunderstand and then finally it's
working on the newer content for the
website and Facebook and stuff like that
to explain this slight shift where up
until maybe a week ago I had split whoop
were collection into the three parts
where it's the politician history
election summary and then what I was
just calling the discussion tool which I
decided that last one was way too broad
and split that out into article review
so like sort of at the lower level
taking an individual piece of content
like assigned to a scientific study or
maybe even some legislation and sort of
pulling it apart to see what is it
actually saying and what do people say
about these various parts and then
eventually the topic overview or that
could be taking that information
something like that vaccines figuring
out what sort of a discussion people
want to have around vaccines but using
those articles that have been reviewed
and summarized as the basis for that
conversation yeah this is my much less
about what people can say about a topic
versus what you can prove what you know
you've actually got stuff to to back up
and so just the content make that a bit
clearer because I think up until now the
content for talking about the discussion
tool was just way too broad and people
didn't really understand what I was
going for which is I mean it is broad
it's hard to have how to how to hone
that down I know there are other
discussion tools out there I can't think
about their names right now Kyle oh okay
with their name
okay I alo is what's coming up in my
brain where it's it's like it's more
like a pro/con like okay this topic and
then you kind of pro/con and then you go
off into pro-kit like yes no and then
yes no on the yes/no is kind of thing
like a branch discussion there's a few
discussion tools out there but they're
not gonna be attached to yours right so
is there a beta version of just the
political piece
that can be launched and with the idea
of like hey we want we want to be able
to add discussions to this using any of
the ones that are out there which I
don't know all of them and people keeper
like did you hear about this project in
this project I'm like yes and no because
I can't keep them all in my brain like I
didn't I need a way to that's why I want
they like Yelp for apps which was gonna
be possibly one of our first projects
together Tech and I think it will
naturally become a project where just
knowing what's out there knowing what
apps exist whether they're from the big
tech giants or they're from a small
group of coders or not-for-profit or our
tech company that I'm created that the
cooperative we're creating show Casey
and like what is it they do how well do
they do it and then contact information
so that like people who have had those
sites right and that might be like maybe
we can reach out to people who have
those discussions sites and say hey want
to come on and discuss what it was like
to create that right what was it like to
create that tool and I assume most of
those people are in it for purpose
instead of profit necessarily even if
they now have to also of course make
profit and maybe I'm wrong and they
don't they don't want to come out or 60
subscribe our channel but doesn't hurt
to try
it doesn't hurt to ask me what's that
yeah if you can get one that one yeah
and if they're you know I think when we
do this for a few weeks and have other
people join us other people who have
tech projects if you missed the
beginning of this we're looking for
other people who have a tech project
that is for purpose instead of profit
over a profit and want to be working
through that project together to
brainstorm to make goals and and move
forward and the more we have people
who've had them in the past have tech
projects currently have had successful
ones then the more were you like
everyone knows everyone it's such a
small group and you know like it's like
my friend has this happened my I am
astounded and I wish I could keep those
connections to be a better networker
like I wish I could remember that but
well you were talking about scientist I
was like I know scientists I went to
school with many scientists and so
if you write up if that is the piece you
want to move forward with then it's
moving forward with that piece if you
want to talk to scientists I and you
write something out I can take them on
Facebook or I can send it directly to
her in there
and say hey I don't even know what your
you're doing currently but I mean
everyone I worked with in the lab I can
I can talk to you and say even just
going to the University and literally
walking around the University in the
science department and saying like hey I
would like to find out like on most of
their doors they have posted with her
their TA hours are and nobody nobody
shows up to them except during finals so
if you could show up to their open hours
to TA is even right like they don't need
to be the person whose names on the lab
but saying hey I'd like to discuss this
and they will love just most of the bowl
of students because you're talking to
them on scientific terms and saying hey
what do you think would be in this right
and if you have I'm not I could have
those conversations but I don't know we
both live in the state I was like in
Kamloops
if you come we can go out to UBC with
you and be part of this conversation
because I might no I don't think I could
have that conversation by myself it's
actually when I was going through
groundswell I was trying to do a vaccine
project and I went and talked to one of
my old professors to say hey what are
these questions and how would this look
like she was very open she said but yeah
if we walk around and see who's who has
hours what they're okay and they'll be
fine with the fact that I don't go there
have never gone there have no both
secondary they're just yeah I mean
you're a tech person right you're
creating tech yeah I I don't care about
those things I have a university degree
and everyone I know who has what it's
like having one is basically just
knowing what you don't know and I think
you already know what you don't know
you're good like okay the see of stuff
that I couldn't possibly understand
gotcha
so we all have to be and they know that
right like that's what going they have a
specialty it's like this is my specialty
and but understanding scientific papers
and understanding what that what that is
is is huge
that's good to know that does sort of
lean on maybe working on the content
it's a bit more important just so that I
can kind of explain it and there you
know there's two or three images to be
like hey here's the stuff that we're
talking about mm-hmm
also maybe the the prototype for that is
like early days they're not really very
interactive because it needs a bunch of
things created to really like dissect
content as far as I've seen don't exist
yeah so it's mostly like just it's more
mock-ups and like things to make
screenshots and here's what it might
look look like so I can sort of do some
of that more just to put together a
quick prep presentation or a couple of
like infographics almost just to give
like I'm really high you know top of the
waves hey here's what we're working on
is this something you'd be interested in
and then I'm so cool then we can dive
deeper and actually ask that these
specific questions that need to get
answered mm-hmm
the other thing I was thinking you were
talking and kind of not listening to you
because you know I'll pre watch it later
listen um beauty of live video is for
either for the politics we could do that
we hit I don't know which you wear
politics even is at UBC but there's a
department for sure and going around and
doing the same thing with TA and saying
hey here's what I'm working on you might
be able to find Poli Sci students who
were like what yeah on board want it now
like I did try to reach out through
email to like exactly that more it was
like to the department heads because we
were they enough they don't post you
know the emails and contents that info
for all the TAS and students but I read
something I didn't hear back that I
assumed yeah they probably get a fair
number of questions and people randomly
reaching out and also that was fairly
early days yeah it would be actually
awesome to um I love giving other people
work because I would never to put like
an advertisement together right like a
little brochure
prints out 100 copies or whatever go go
to UBC it handed out at the poly side
place and say hey is this a project
you'd want to be in on and and then do
the TA thing like go to them and say
maybe just give them the paper but then
also if there's like a random student
who happens to be there for the TA hours
which it's like a unicorn event Oh
unless things have changed the last time
but I think it's the weird part because
we're so electronic right even our
projects are electronic reach you don't
via email is so cold and then when you
go and get warm warm contact where
you're like I'm a human being who cares
about things too and I'm in it you you
can see that they're in it for purpose
even if they're in it for profit too
right like like they're not necessarily
gonna care that you're in it for profit
they're like what I am BG for
politicians yes that needs to exist and
they might know of ones that have
already existed contact those people and
find out because you know they have and
find out but they are things that like
are closed up when I first launched my
Kickstarter I got a lot of questions
about that have you checked this have
you checked that out and most of them I
had and you know I still didn't think
that they were quite where I thought
they needed them to be but it was cool
to see people were at least that engaged
and there were a couple that I hadn't
heard of that I went and looked at and
today every cool and yeah getting an
intro to something like that even if it
was just somebody who was you know like
a user that posted a lot of stuff on
those apps but still be useful yeah I'm
remembering now that I've been graduated
for almost 20 years in a while but I'm
like all these people who are in Poli
Sci or who are in science and Poli
science are also extreme social media
people probably right like they probably
can do that piece of it can probably
find the marketing that you and I maybe
aren't aren't the best at and if you
have those people on board right like
the next kickstarter you do has power
behind it right they might already be
influencers on Instagram and Twitter and
and doing those things but that's that's
just if they you know if it happens to
be that way right the 20 year olds that
Susan University like it's like grew up
with the internet like they were born in
2000 Adriel so we're coming up to 30
minutes do we want to say what we're
committed to doing for the next week
sure so it sounds like I'd want to build
up the content start being able to have
those in-person conversations I doubt it
will be ready
but and because that's actually a fair
amount of stuff but at least you know
have a better idea on what kind of
content is needed and have the framework
and then possibly talk about that and
maybe some really basic mock-ups just to
sort of say does that make sense to you
not you know it would it would be pretty
it's just to sort of say here's the
basic idea
he doesn't make sense to you is your you
know as you said one of them scientists
and somebody who's not super close to
the you know down in the weeds part of
the project which in this case is good
because it means you know you already
know more about it than they would but
if it makes sense to you and hopefully
it'll be more likely to make sense to
them yeah sounds cool um when I was
doing life coaching and stuff and doing
this with like people not outside of
tech we had what were called SMART goals
which were specific measurable
attainable realistic and time-based this
is not that right cuz you could I don't
know we want to make them SMART goals as
far as that just means like I will work
on this for three hours by next Saturday
right like it just means cuz I we aren't
gonna know whether to check this off or
not because it's like move forward a
little bit right if you're good with
that I'm good with that because I might
be how am i some of my goals are but do
you want to put a um something on them
like well um sure yeah we can say I
think three hours actually sounds good
three hours okay you're gonna work on
making a mock-up or create creating
building out more content for three
hours between now and then geared
towards having those in person
discussions and starting to actually you
know get people at various universities
involved in both sides of the project
okay perfect um and that's that you're
just gonna commit to one thing I don't
think that's a problem you also have a
full-time job you're doing that's like
three hours yeah okay so I'm committing
to posting today in the parenting group
for specifically for parenting and
neurodiversity creating like I want to
find one person to have a conversation
with and then we will invite other
people I also
and it has to be today cuz it's Saturday
I can't post it any other day the other
thing I want to do is kind of look at my
own life and pick three topics like Rho
diversity disability and parenting look
I already picked them um that pertained
to me and are also something I want to
discuss on an ongoing basis
maybe game be and then reach out to
those communities specifically and maybe
even pick a time period where we're
doing it every week and and then you
hopefully keep happy guests coming back
and whether it's doing that or just
putting it out to those communities and
saying hey I want to find one person who
is committed to coming like weekly pick
a time period and the issue is this is
what I do I'm like three of them I'm
like I don't wanna commit to three weeks
that's ridiculous and so but if I find
one of them from one of those hotspots
in my life great that's the one the
universe told me to focus on for idea
cafe the issue is sometimes the universe
over don't forgive so that I'm like okay
some of them will fall away I can do
three only five conversations though
those three this one and my Friday one
but you know that's not actually a lot
that's five hours of work right so I
mean honestly that's that's you know if
you ever want a special guest for the
neurodiversity conversation as well ya
know and that's like the people can
connected to so many of them and doing
one off ones I also want to say just sit
with the ones that are more powerful
like the like the Kurdish genocide and
the ones like how what does that look
like what does it look like to be a
facilitator of a conversation that I'm
not part of and how do I reach out to
those people because those people are a
little bit one-off right they're not
gonna talk about the same thing
necessarily every week but what does it
look like to have a conversation about a
question around people are affected
maybe this isn't the right format maybe
this is not gonna hold the space
properly but there's something calling
me to it something that's like no this
is this is why we're creating it like to
be able to connect over the mundane like
neurodiversity which is not mundane but
at the same time is like your day-in
day-out struggle your data
you've genocide it kind of is yeah yeah
exactly and then the big things like war
and and even even things like cancer and
like okay well what what did you learn
from it what did like so I guess it's
sitting with it and saying are there
effective questions that are going to be
talking about things that aren't already
out there that aren't and yes the
difference just watching this last week
a bunch of documentaries on disabilities
from like 20 20 and 60 minutes and stuff
and it's always so ablest like this
person is brought with strife and it's
like never versus watching special books
with special kids this guy Chris schumer
who does these amazing interviews and
he's just got like a soul for and you
fall in love with them and it's their
story and I'm like those are completely
opposite like one is just like the
opposite of inspiration porn it's like
which is bad enough in and of itself
which is like look at this person
struggling in a wheelchair looks like
gonna head
yes per asian porn of thing maybe yeah
like it's like Oh feel better that
you're not these horrible people who
have this genetic condition and it's
like it's seems like a very modern media
approach like the kind of trying to help
by generating buzz but they're doing it
by saying like what was them they're so
terribly honest and which is what you
have to do in your for profit right when
you're like trying to get more people in
but they're okay it's okay they're okay
they have they have a lot of positive in
their life that it's like either they're
there to inspire you because they
overcame something or they're there to
make you feel better about your life and
they're not they're there to live their
life and giving people tools to be able
to share their stories with one another
is what I want idea cafe to be so right
so pick three topics which I got already
did and just sit with the hard stuff
and decide what that looks like and I'm
not making those measurable anyway
because the other thing I'm doing is um
I gave up smoking pot as of Tuesday was
I said goodbye it went Monday Tuesday I
did a lot of it and then until the new
year so for till January first I'm not
at least I'm not smoking pot and I'm
also meditating daily and doing yoga
daily doing a 30-minute scope on
for Friday and because it's brand-new I
feel like I don't want to commit to too
much and I feel like these are things
that I can I can do cuz I can do them
all right before before you come so I'm
gonna say goodbye to our live viewers
and then we can go off and chat a little
bit more once we're not recording if
anyone would like to join us and be part
of having a Saturday morning
conversation or whatever it is in your
time zone at this same time time period
to discuss your project and how you want
help moving it forward from each other
from the crowd and just have a space to
to be held accountable so thank you and
we will see you next week